paktribune.com 2018-12-28

# Privacy Statement - PakTribune

We will collect no personal information about you when you visit our website unless you choose to provide that information to us.  
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We automatically collect and store only the following information about your visit:

1\. The internet domain (for example, "xcompany.com" if you use a private Internet access account, or "yourschool.edu" if you connect from a university's domaine) and IP address ( an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web) from which you access our website;

2\. The date and time you access our site;

3\. The pages you visit;

4\. If you linked to this website from another website, the address of that other website.

If you choose to provide us with personal information by sending an e-mail to us, or by filling out a form with your personal information and submitting it through our website, we use that information to respond to your message and to help us get the information you have requested. We do not collect personal information for any other purposes. Moreover, we do not create individual profiles with the information you provide or give this information to any private organizations. Nor do we collect information for commercial marketing.
